Deyan Denev



Personal Details

Deyan Denev

Jan van Riebeekstraat 4 1059ZW Amsterdam

+31 631243386

denev.s.deyan@gmail.com

Date of birth: 14 January 1983

Nationality: Bulgarian

Skills

Business Acumen Result-oriented Go getter Microsoft Office SPSS



Languages

English Bulgarian Spanish Russian



Hobbies and Interests

- Playing Football
- Cooking
- History

Profile

Main focus of my professional background includes sales support of business-to-business activities and achieving targets for growth. My professional mindset is based on the realization of commercial goals and delivering results. Current key responsibilities include achieving targets for growth and customer satisfaction. More earlier experience includes also tasks to deliver support to other team members and after-sales monitoring.

Education

MSc Business Administration (completed)

09/2016 - 02/2018

University of Amsterdam

MSc Finance (completed)

2011 - 2014

University of National and World Economy, Sofia, Bulgaria

BA History and Ethnolgy (completed)

2001 - 2005

University of Sofia, Bulgaria

Work Experience

CS Partner Specialist

03/2018 - present

Booking.com, Amsterdam

- Provide commercial advice to business partners ranging from large hotels to small and medium business owners
- Deliver on-time technical and sales support to business partners

Mortgage Sales Team Leader

01/2015 - 08/2016

Postbank (postbank.bg), Sofia, Bulgaria

- Accomplishment on a team level of double-digit percentage growth in six consecutive quarters (2015 and Q1/Q2 2016)
- To monitor and provide support of 200+ small and medium business accounts and foster long-term relationship across sales channels
- Accountable for achieving team targets for KPIs mainly related to time-to-money and time-to-market

Sales Manager Distribution Channels

08/2012 - 12/2014

Postbank, Sofia, Bulgaria

- To monitor and support 50+ large business accounts across sales channels
- To navigate strategies for penetration of new market niches and key demographics
- Direct reporting on monthly, quarterly and on-demand basis to the sales department manager and the business unit manager

Morgage Sales Expert

07/2006 - 07/2012

Postbank, Sofia, Bulgaria

- Key responsibility realization of commercial targets
- To generate sales leads and provide financial advise to customers

References

References available upon request.